armadamusic.com 2019-12-08

# PRIVACY STATEMENT & SECURITY | Armada Music - Home to the music you love

Version 0.2- On the 4th of March 2019 this page has been updated.

Your personal data will be processed and protected in accordance with the Dutch data protection  
legislation and the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). On this page you can read  
which data we collect when you visit our website, why we collect these data and how we  
improve your experience using our website based on these data. So you will understand how  
we work.

This privacy statement applies to the services of www.armadamusic.com. By using our  
website you acknowledge to accept our privacy statement. In case there are links to third  
party websites or sources on our website, you must realize that www.armadamusic.com is  
not responsible for the privacy statement of other websites and other sources.

**PURPOSE OF THE COLLECTED DATA**  
Armada only processes your private data for the specific purposes that these data have been  
provided for by you to us, unless we have received your permission to do otherwise.  
www.armadamusic.com respects the privacy of all the visitors/users of its website and  
ensures that all personal information which you will give us, will be dealt with in a strict  
confidential manner. Also we will not file these data for longer than necessary and allowed by law.  
Data are collected for the following purposes:

  * Newsletters, e-mails, competitions and events and invites.
  * Order one of our services/products These data will be used to execute your order. These data will be stored on a security server owned by www.armadamusic.com or by a third party. We will not combine your personal data with other data.
  * Execute contracts.
  * Accounting and payments

**ACCESS AND STORAGE OF DATA**  
Your personal data will be stored on a secured server owned by www.armadamusic.com or  
by an trusted and approved third party on base of a processing agreement. We will not  
combine your personal data with other data and we will only pass on your data to other  
parties if this is really necessary for our services. This may include parties such as: delivery  
partners, payment partners, IT service providers. In suspicious situations we are obliged to  
share customer data with government agencies.  
The parties who are allowed access to your data may only use these data to provide you with  
a service on behalf of Armada. We never sell your data to third parties.  
We store your data in our secured databases located in the EU. We always apply strict  
security measures. In the case that personal data are transferred to countries outside the   
European Union, we ensure that your privacy is protected. We make sure that American  
parties are registered under the Privacy Shield.

**TERM OF DATA STORAGE**  
We do not store and use your data longer than necessary. We will delete all data we have  
from you as soon as the purpose has expired. Or we use your data anonymously, because we  
need certain data for internal analyses and reports.  
For the term of storage we keep the following deadlines, after which we delete your data:

  * We will not store camera images of our offices for more than 4 weeks. Unless we see something suspicious that we have to further investigate whether the images should be kept longer because of a legal obligation.
  * We are entitled to delete inactive client accounts (after 7 years).After that period we only use your data anonymously, for internal reports.
  * Due to tax regulations we keep our administration with your financial data for a term of 7 years.

**COOKIES**  
We collect data for research to get a better insight in our clients in order to tailor our  
services/products.  
This websites uses cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in  
a user’s web browser while the user is browsing the website. Every time the user loads the  
website, the browser sends the cookie back to the server to notify the website of the user’s  
previous activity. This information gathered by the cookie will be stored on the security  
server of www.armadamusic.com or by a third party. We use this information to see how you  
use the website and to make reports on website activity in order to offer you other services  
and products related to your activity on internet. Some cookie developers have access to the  
data that cookies collect on our website. You can read more about this in our cookie  
statement and the privacy statement of these parties.

**SWITCH OFF COOKIES**  
Most browsers are set up to accept cookies but you can set up your browser to refuse  
cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being sent to you. It is however possible that some  
services and functions on our website and on other website do not function properly when  
you have switched off cookies on your browser.

**THIRD PARTIES**  
We will not provide your data to other parties. In some cases your data will be shared  
internally but our personnel signed a non-disclosure contract to respect the confidentiality of  
your personal data.

**ALTERATIONS**  
This privacy statement is tuned to the current status of our website. Adjustments or changes  
on our website can lead to changes in the privacy statement. So we advise you to read our  
privacy statement on a regular basis.

**PERSONAL DATA OPTIONS**  
We offer all visitors the possibility to look at, to change or to delete all personal data which  
has been provided to us.

**ADJUSTMENTS AND TERMINATION/REMOVAL OF NEWSLETTER**  
At the bottom of all our mails you will find the possibility to adjust your personal data or to  
terminate the newsletter.

**ADJUSTMENTS/REMOVAL COMMUNICATION**  
If you would like to alter your personal data or to remove these from our files then you can  
contact us. See below for contact information.

**_QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK_**  
We check on a regular basis if we comply with the privacy statement. If you have questions  
about our privacy policy do contact us:  
Armada Music B.V.  
P.O. Box 75247  
1070AE Amsterdam  
The Netherlands.  
T: +31 20 408 0846  
E-mail: privacy@armadamusic.com  
Chamber of commerce number: 27257612  
VAT identification number: NL8141.86.518.B.01
